Guide to the Yale University Master of Fine Arts Theses in Photography
Yale University Arts Library
- MFA Theses
  - [Untitled], 1990; Turczan, Katherine; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs, platinum prints; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 100)
  - [Untitled], 1991; Abrams, Rebecca; 12 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 101)
  - [Untitled], 1991; Berridge, Mary; 12 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 102)
    Keywords: portraits, families, New Haven
  - [Untitled], 1991; Edwards, Jennifer; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 103)
    Keywords: portraits, families, documentary photography
  - [Untitled], 1991; Hintz, Thomas; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 104)
  - [Untitled], 1991; Letinsky, Laura; 12 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 105)
  - [Untitled], 1991; Williams, Jennette; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 106)
    Keywords: portraits, children (people by age group), families
  - [Untitled], 1992; Ahlgren, Steven; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 107)
  - [Untitled], 1992; Berenfield, Yosefa; 13 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 list of works; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 11 x 14 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 108)
    Keywords: portraits, landscapes (representations), nature photography
  - [Untitled], 1992; Dixon, Charlotte; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 111)
    Keywords: still lifes, abstract (fine arts style), landscapes (representations), nature photography
  - [Untitled], 1992; Fowler, Eve; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches, including mat (Box 109)
  - [Untitled], 1992; Fusaro, Rita; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 110)
    Keywords: portraits, children (people by age group)
  - [Untitled], 1992; Sklar, Evan; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 112)
    Keywords: still lifes
  - Prysia's Garden, 1992; Suchy, Lida; 14 prints, 1 submission form, 1 miscellaneous doc; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 11 x 14 inches (Box 113)
    Keywords: portraits, landscapes (representations), still lifes
  - [Untitled], 1993; Altshuler, Sharyn; 23 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 115)
    Keywords: documentary photography, women (female humans)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Bey-Smikle, Dawoud; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 16 x 20 inches, including mat (Box 116)
    Keywords: photomosaics (photographs), portraits; See also Box 117.
  - [Untitled], 1993; Bey, Dawoud, 1953- (Box 117)
    See also Box 116.
  - [Untitled], 1993; Calabrese, Leonard; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 118)
    Keywords: portraits, urban areas
  - [Untitled], 1993; Fernandez, Hugo; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 119)
    Keywords: nudes (representations), women (female humans), photomosaics (photographs)
  - Group (Grey) Photography Project, 1993; 10; books of photographs; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 12.5 x 12.5 inches (Box 120)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Hill, Karen; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 121)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Johnson, Veronica; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 122)
    Keywords: close-up views, still lifes, abstract (fine arts style)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Lê, An-My; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 123)
    Keywords: sculpture (visual work), still lifes, photomosaics (photographs), figures (representation)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Pilson, John Carter; 12 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 124)
  - [Untitled], 1993; Reiff, Patricia; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 125)
    Keywords: nature photography, landscapes (representations), townscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 1994; Baum, Erica; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 126)
    Keywords: abstract (fine arts style), close-up views
  - [Untitled], 1994; Brodsky, Alexandra S.; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 127)
    Keywords: still lifes, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1994; Hilliard, David; 7 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 9 x 14 inches to 7.5 x 35 inches (Box 128)
    Keywords: photomosaics (photographs), landscapes (representations), portraits
  - [Untitled], 1994; Linehan, James; 11 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 129)
    Keywords: portraits, landscapes (representations), interior views
  - [Untitled], 1994; Monastra, Carolyn; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 130)
  - [Untitled], 1994; Rubin, Seth; 19 prints, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 16 x 20 inches to 20 x 24 inches (Box 131)
    Keywords: close-up views, abstract (fine arts style), figures (representation), studio
  - [Untitled], 1994; Snauffer, Wendy; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 132)
    Keywords: still lifes, landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 1994; Weeks, Eric; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 133)
  - [Untitled], 1995; Beirne, Chris; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 134)
    Keywords: medical centers, interior views
  - [Untitled], 1995; Gaskell, Anna; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 8 inches to 8 x 10 inches (Box 135)
    Keywords: portraits, close-up views
  - [Untitled], 1995; Glushien, Scott; 11 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 136)
    Keywords: still lifes, portraits, abstract (fine arts style)
  - [Untitled], 1995; Krajewska, Elzbieta (Elka); 18 prints, 4 artist statements, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 137)
  - [Untitled], 1995; Miller, Brian David; 14 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 138)
    Keywords: nature photography, manipulated photographs
  - [Untitled], 1995; Mesa-Pelly, Deborah; 12 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 139)
    Keywords: fantasy, portraits, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 1995; So-Chen, Gretchen; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 140)
    Keywords: Hong Kong, landscapes (representations), documentary photography, interior views
  - [Untitled], 1995; Turounet, Paul; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 141)
    Keywords: travel photography, landscapes (representations), cityscapes (representations), portraits
  - [Untitled], 1996; Albert, Gail; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 142)
  - [Untitled], 1996; Castellanos, Patricia; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 143)
    Keywords: figures (representations), portraits, close-up views, interior views
  - [Untitled], 1996; Gage, Jenny; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 144)
  - Photographs of Puerto Rico, 1996; Gonzalez, Larry; 15 prints, 1 submission form, 1 miscellaneous doc; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 8 x 30 inches (Box 145)
    Keywords: Puerto Rico, landscapes (representations), interior views, photomosaics (photographs), panoramas
  - [Untitled], 1996; Kokkinias, Panos; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 146)
    Keywords: portraits, still lifes, interior views
  - [Untitled], 1996; Lin, Shu Fen; 10 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 149)
  - [Untitled], 1996; Lussier, Thomas; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 8 inches to 8 x 10 inches (Box 147)
  - [Untitled], 1996; Moriarty, Brian; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 148)
    Keywords: close-up views, still lifes, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1997; Bezzubov, Sasha; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 150)
    Keywords: documentary photography, women (female humans), New York City, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1997; Burns, Laura; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 16 x 20 inches, including mat (Box 151)
    Keywords: close-up views, interior views, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1997; Forman, Alexandra; 20 prints, 1 submission form, 1 miscellaneous document; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 152)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), figures (representations), close-up views
  - [Untitled], 1997; Hoey, Dana; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 153)
  - [Untitled], 1997; Joo, Eun Suk; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 154)
  - [Untitled], 1997; Salzinger, Samantha; 20 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 155)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), interior views, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 1997; Soderquist, Hans H.; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 156)
    Keywords: portraits, adolescence, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 1997; Torop, Daniel; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 157)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), rural areas, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1998; Brandt, Gabriel; parts 1 and 2, 27 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 11 x 14 inches to 20 x 24 inches (Box 158)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), architecture (object genre), documentary photography; See also Box 159.
  - [Untitled], 1998; Brandt, Gabriel (Box 159)
    See also Box 158.
  - [Untitled], 1998; Core, Sharon; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 160)
    Keywords: still lifes, portraits, nature photography
  - [Untitled], 1998; Kurland, Justine; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 161)
    Keywords: portraits, adolescence, documentary photography, women (female humans)
  - [Untitled], 1998; Marder, Malerie; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 162)
  - [Untitled], 1998; Peterman, Scott; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 163)
    Keywords: nature photography, landscapes (representations), portraits
  - [Untitled], 1998; Roy, Lisa; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 164)
    Keywords: architecture (object genre), interior views, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 1998; Wendt, William; 1 print, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 31 x 88.5 inches (Box 165)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), nature photography, urban areas
  - [Untitled], 1999; Davies, Alison; 22; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 166)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), portraits
  - [Untitled], 1999; Ducklo, Matthew; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 167)
  - [Untitled], 1999; Fey, Caleb; 24 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 8 x 10 inches to 11 x 14 inches (Box 168)
    Keywords: self-portraiture, portraits
  - [Untitled], 1999; Grannan, Katy; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 169)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), women (female humans)
  - [Untitled], 1999; Portocarrero, Nestor; 13 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 170)
    Keywords: portraits, nudes (representations), abstract (fine arts style)
  - [Untitled], 1999; Sakoun, Rebecca; 4 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 171)
    Keywords: portraits, abstract (fine arts style), studio portraits
  - [Untitled], 1999; Sambunaris, Victoria; 18 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 172)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), industrial districts, architecture (object genre)
  - [Untitled], 1999; Wynne, Jessica; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 173)
  - [Untitled], 1999; Zachai, Mateo Zapata; 1 VHS, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; video art (Box 175)
    Master copy VHS located in Box 174. Use copy VHS and DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled: "Caleb," "Afternoon," and "Divorce."
  - [Untitled], 2000; Barclay, Hughes; 30 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 10.5 x 14 inches (Box 176)
    Keywords: New York, portraits, cityscapes (representations)
  - Ground Notes, 2000; Ebner, Shannon Philayne; 4 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 177)
    Keywords: documentary photography, portraits, abstract (fine arts style)
  - [Untitled], 2000; Kereszi, Lisa; 20; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 204)
    Keywords: close-up views, still lifes, interior views
  - [Untitled], 2000; Miner, Christopher; 10 VHS, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; video art (Box 178)
    Master copy VHS located in Box 178. Use copy VHS and DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled: "Self-Portrait," "Auction," "Hetrodyne," "Identifying With Nature," "Dream," "Led By the Child," "Virgin," "Disconnect," and "Me, God, and Sandra."
  - [Untitled], 2000; Murray, Katie; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 179)
    Keywords: portraits, documentary photography, Queens New York
  - [Untitled], 2000; Ou, Arthur (Box 244)
    Master copy CD located in Box 244. Box 244 also includes original wooden box. Use copy CD located in Box 175. See also Box 245.
  - [Untitled], 2000; Ou, Arthur; 15 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 245)
    Keywords: documentary photography, manipulated photographs; See also Box 244.
  - [Untitled], 2000; Raila, Marc; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 180)
    Keywords: still lifes, close-up views, photomosaics (photographs)
  - [Untitled], 2000; West, Angela; 23 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 5 x 7 inches to 8 x 10 inches (Box 181)
  - [Untitled], 2001; Davis, Tim; 30 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 182)
    Keywords: night photography, close-up views
  - [Untitled], 2001; Donaldson, Benjamin; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 183)
    Keywords: portraits, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2001; Maida, Joseph; 24 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs, black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; range from 11 x 14 inches to 20 x 24 inches (Box 184)
    Master copy VHS located in Box 174. Use copy VHS and DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled, "Parade" and "Hotshots."
  - [Untitled], 2001; Martinson, Tia; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 185)
  - [Untitled], 2001; Nakadate, Laurel; 1 VHS, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; video art (Box 174)
    Master copy VHS located in Box 174. Use copy VHS and DVD located in Box 175. Videos are titled: "Pet," "Birthday," "OOPS!," "Spring," and "Secret Girl Scout."
  - [Untitled], 2001; Pecchio, Pamela; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 personal note; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 186)
    Keywords: portraits, still lifes, landscapes (representations), nature photography
  - [Untitled], 2001; Shteynshleyger, Anna; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 187)
    Master copy VHS located in Box 174. Use copy VHS and DVD located in Box 175. Video is titled, "Conversation."
  - [Untitled], 2001; Whetstone, Jeff; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 188)
  - [Untitled], 2001; Wyse, Mark; 30 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 book of photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 189)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Beshty, Walead; 15 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 5 personal photographs; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 4.5 x 11.5 inches to 14 x 22 inches (Box 190)
    Keywords: portraits, photomosaics (photographs), nudes (representations), landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Cobb, Catherine; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 191)
    Keywords: portraits, women (female humans), nature photography
  - Paper Airplanes, 2002; Chiedo, Jeffrey; 33 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 192)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Darpli, Sarah; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 193)
  - Breaking Up with Knoxville, 2002; Martin, Sarah; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 194)
    Keywords: Knoxville, TN, portraits, landscapes (representations)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Recktenwald, Eric; 16 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 195)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Tyler, Laura; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; black-and-white photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 196)
    Keywords: sculpture (visual work), architecture (object genre), manipulated photographs, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2002; Weathersby, Ann; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 personal photograph; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 197)
  - [Untitled], 2002; Willhide, Melanie; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 list of works; color photographs; Measurements:; 8 x 10 inches (Box 198)
  - [Untitled], 2003; Collette, Anna; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 199)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), architecture (object genre), urban areas
  - [Untitled], 2003; de Koning, Heather; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 201)
  - [Untitled], 2003; Gunhouse, Carl; 17 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 200)
    Keywords: nature photography, portraits
  - [Untitled], 2003; McDermott, Jennifer; 22 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 202)
    Keywords: portraits, nature photography, still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2003; Miller, Meredith; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 203)
    Keywords: portraits, women (female humans), still lifes
  - [Untitled], 2003; Pisciotta, Philip; 21 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 13 x 20 inches to 16 x 20 inches (Box 205)
  - [Untitled], 2003; Strassheim, Angela; 33 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 16 x 20 inches (Box 206)
    Keywords: interior views, portraits, forensic photography
  - [Untitled], 2003; Vahrenwald, Michael; 31 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 207)
    Keywords: landscapes (representations), interior views, townscapes (representations), architecture (object genre)
  - [Untitled], 2003; Wolkoff, Katherine; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 20 x 24 inches (Box 208)
  - [Untitled], 2004; Andersen, Jonnie; 21 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form, 1 miscellaneous document; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 209)
  - [Untitled], 2004; Bass, Samantha; 24 prints, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 12.5 x 16 inches (Box 210)
    Keywords: still lifes, close-up views, domestic animals, rural areas
  - [Untitled], 2004; Connors, Mathew; 19 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 13 x 18.5 inches (Box 211)
    Keywords: urban areas, cityscapes (representations), documentary photography, manipulated photographs
  - Tree Planting, 2004; Johnson, Sarah; 20 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; range from 9.5 x 9.5 inches to 19.5 x 23.25 inches (Box 212)
    Keywords: portraits, landscapes (representations), nature photography, models (representation)
  - [Untitled], 2004; Monteith, Matthew; 28 prints, 1 artist statement, 1 submission form; color photographs; Measurements:; 11 x 14 inches (Box 213)